Guide to the New York State College of Agriculture 4-H club records, 1918-2018.
New York State College of Agriculture 4-H club records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State College of Agriculture 4-H Club Records, 1918-2018.
21-24-692
New York State College of Agriculture. Extension Service.
64.7 cubic feet.
Reports, correspondence, programs, minutes, announcements, circular letters, photographs, scrapbooks, films, printed material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Mainly annual reports of the various New York State county 4-H Club agents.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Mainly annual reports of the various New York State county 4-H Club agents, consisting of mimeographed and printed forms providing statistical data concerning membership, projects, and agents' activities, typescript, and "Narrative Reports" which the agents wrote to summarize and interpret the results accomplished and the extension methods used. Some reports include photographs and newspaper clippings; also, correspondence, programs, minutes, reports, announcements, circular letters, photographs and printed material concerning the State Leaders' Training Camps, the New York State 4-H Health Committee, 4-H Clubs at the New York State Fair, annual State 4-H Club congresses, the New York State 4-H Extension Federation, the Older Rural Youth and Young Adult Programs, Junior Field Days at Cornell University, and annual conferences of the Extension Service and the county 4-H agents; correspondents include F. E. Heinzelman and Professor William J. Wright, club leaders, Albert Hoefer, State 4-H Club leader and director of the State Leaders' Training Camps, and W. Jack Weaver, assistant in the Agricultural Education Bureau of the State Education Department. Also, scrapbooks of clippings and photographs (6 volumes, 1931-1953) pertaining to the activities and accomplishments of the various New York State county 4-H Clubs and their members, including photographs of Franklin and Eleanor Roosevelt, and a box of films.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Agriculture.; Heinzelman, F. E.; Hoefer, Albert.; Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945.; Weaver, W. Jack (William Jack), b.1890.; Wright, W.J. (William Joseph), b.1881.; New York State 4-H Extension Federation.; New York State 4-H Health Committee.
Subjects:
Agricultural extension work.; County agricultural agents.; 4-H clubs--New York (State); Youth--Societies and clubs.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Scrapbooks.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
See also collections #23-2-749, New York State College of Home Economics records; and #21-24-1975, Cornell University Cooperative Extension records
The film Learning for the Future: 4-H in New York City from this collection has been digitized and can be found on Cornell's Library Media Space website along with other Home Economics and related films.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Annual Reports
Series II. Program Files
Series III. 4-H Club Records
A. 16 mm Films
B. Videotapes and Discs
C. Records
D. County Programs/Records
Series IV. Newsletters and other Publications
Series V. Photographs
A. Club Camps
B. Shows
C. Projects
D. Meetings, National Congress, County Groups
E. Clubs
F. Shops
G. Fairs and Field Days
H. Exhibits and Demonstrations
I. Canning
J. Various Subjects
Series VI. Memorabilia and Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Annual Reports
  - County annual reports, 1918-1922 (Box 1)
  - County annual reports, 1922-1923 (Box 2)
  - County annual reports, 1923-1924 (Box 3)
  - County annual reports, 1923-1924 (Box 4)
  - County annual reports, 1924-1925 (Box 5)
  - County annual reports, 1925-1926 (Box 6)
  - County annual reports, 1926 (Box 7)
  - County annual reports, 1926-1927 (Box 8)
  - County annual reports, 1927 (Box 9)
  - County annual reports, 1928 (Box 10)
  - County annual reports, 1928-1929 (Box 11)
  - County annual reports, 1928-1929 (Box 12)
  - County annual reports, 1931 (Box 13)
  - County annual reports, 1931-1932 (Box 14)
  - County annual reports, 1932 (Box 15)
  - County annual reports, 1932-1933 (Box 16)
  - County annual reports, 1933 (Box 17)
  - County annual reports, 1934 (Box 18)
  - County annual reports, 1934 (Box 19)
  - County annual reports, 1934-1935 (Box 20)
  - County Annual Reports, 1935 (Box 21)
  - County annual reports, 1936 (Box 22)
  - County annual reports, 1936 (Box 23)
  - County annual reports, 1936-1937 (Box 24)
  - County annual reports, 1937 (Box 25)
  - County annual reports, 1937 (Box 26)
  - County annual reports, 1938 (Box 27)
  - County annual reports, 1938 (Box 28)
  - County annual reports, 1938 (Box 29)
  - County annual reports, 1939 (Box 30)
  - County annual reports, 1939 (Box 31)
  - County annual reports, 1939 (Box 32)
  - County annual reports, 1939-1940 (Box 33)
  - County annual reports, 1940 (Box 34)
  - County annual reports, 1940 (Box 35)
  - County annual reports, 1940 (Box 36)
  - County annual reports, 1940 (Box 37)
  - County annual reports, 1941 (Box 38)
  - County annual reports, 1941 (Box 39)
  - County annual reports, 1941 (Box 40)
  - County annual reports, 1941 (Box 41)
  - County annual reports, 1942 (Box 42)
  - County annual reports, 1942 (Box 43)
  - County annual reports, 1942 (Box 44)
  - County annual reports, 1943 (Box 45)
  - County annual reports, 1943 (Box 46)
  - County annual reports, 1943 (Box 47)
  - County annual reports, 1944 (Box 48)
  - County annual reports, 1944 (Box 49)
  - County annual reports, 1944 (Box 50)
  - County annual reports, 1945-1945 (Box 51)
  - County annual reports, 1945 (Box 52)
  - County annual reports, 1945 (Box 53)
  - County annual reports, 1946 (Box 54)
  - County annual reports, 1946 (Box 55)
  - County annual reports, 1936-1947 (Box 56)
  - County annual reports, 1947 (Box 57)
  - County annual reports, 1947 (Box 58)
  - County annual reports, 1947-1948 (Box 59)
  - County annual reports, 1948 (Box 60)
  - County annual reports, 1948 (Box 61)
  - County annual reports, 1948-1949 (Box 62)
  - County annual reports, 1949 (Box 63)
  - County annual reports, 1949 (Box 64)
  - County annual reports, 1949-1950 (Box 65)
  - County annual reports, 1950 (Box 66)
  - County annual reports, 1950 (Box 67)
  - County annual reports, 1950-1951 (Box 68)
  - County annual reports, 1951 (Box 69)
  - County annual reports, 1951 (Box 70)
  - County annual reports, 1951-1952 (Box 71)
  - County annual reports, 1952 (Box 72)
  - County annual reports, 1952 (Box 73)
  - County annual reports, 1952 (Box 74)
  - County annual reports, 1953 (Box 75)
  - County annual reports, 1953 (Box 76)
  - County annual reports, 1953 (Box 77)
  - County annual reports, 1953 (Box 78)
  - County annual reports, 1954 (Box 79)
  - County annual reports, 1954 (Box 80)
  - County annual reports, 1954 (Box 81)
  - County annual reports, 1954 (Box 82)
  - County annual reports, 1954-1955 (Box 83)
  - County annual reports, 1955 (Box 84)
  - County annual reports, 1955 (Box 85)
  - County annual reports, 1955 (Box 86)
  - County annual reports, 1955 (Box 87)
  - County annual reports, 1956 (Box 88)
  - County annual reports, 1956 (Box 89)
  - County annual reports, 1956 (Box 90)
  - County annual reports, 1956 (Box 91)
  - County annual reports, 1957 (Box 91)
  - County annual reports, 1957 (Box 92)
  - County annual reports, 1957 (Box 93)
  - County annual reports, 1957 (Box 94)
  - County annual reports, 1957 (Box 95)
  - County annual reports, 1957 (Box 96)
  - County annual reports, 1958 (Box 97)
  - County annual reports, 1958 (Box 98)
  - County annual reports, 1958 (Box 99)
  - County annual reports, 1958 (Box 100)
  - County annual reports, 1958 (Box 101)
  - County annual reports, 1959 (Box 102)
  - County annual reports, 1959-1960 (Box 103)
  - County annual reports, 1960-1961 (Box 104)
  - County annual reports, 1962-1963 (Box 105)
  - County annual reports, 1963-1964 (Box 106)
  - County annual reports, 1964-1965 (Box 107)
  - County annual reports, 1965-1967 (Box 108)
  - County annual reports, 1967-1968 (Box 109)
  - County annual reports (Box 110)
  - County monthly reports, 1969 (Box 110)
  - Annual narrative reports (book) New York State Agricultural Extension with material on early history of New York State Farm Bureau, 1914-1920 (Box 131)
  - New York State annual reports of 4-H club work, 1918-1941 (Box 111)
  - New York State annual reports of 4-H club work, 1941-1963 (Box 112)
  - Annual report- older youth program, 1946 (Box 114)
  - Annual report- older youth program, 1947 (Box 114)
  - Annual report- older youth program, 1948 (Box 114)
  - Annual report- 4-H young adult program- New York, 1949 (Box 114)
  - Annual report- 4-H young adult program- New York, 1950 (Box 114)
  - Annual report- 4-H young adult program- New York, 1950 (Box 114)
  - Annual report- 4-H young adult program- New York, 1950 (Box 114)
  - Report- Edna Sommerfeld- young adult program, 1950; 1951 (Box 114)
  - Annual report- 4-H young adult program- New York, 1951 (Box 114)
  - Annual report 4-H young adult program- New York, 1953 (Box 114)
  - Annual 4-H youth enrollment reports, 1965-1969 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Annual 4-H youth enrollment reports, 1969-1972 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Annual 4-H youth enrollment reports, 1972-1977 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Annual 4-H youth enrollment reports, 1977-1978 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Annual 4-H youth enrollment reports, 1978-1979 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Annual 4-H youth enrollment reports, 1979-1980 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Annual 4-H youth enrollment reports, 1980-1981 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Annual 4-H youth enrollment reports, 1981-1983 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Annual 4-H youth enrollment reports, 1983-1986 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Annual 4-H youth enrollment reports, 2005-2006, 2006-2007, 2008-2009 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Annual 4-H youth enrollment reports- ES 237, 2010-2014; DVD-1188 (Box 144)
  - Annual reports - 4-H, 2003, 2004, 2005, 2007 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Annual report - 4-H, 2005; CD-3853
    Carmichael, Celeste
- Series II. Program Files
  - Letter about 4-H pin, 1928 (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - State Fair, 1920-1943; State Leaders Training Camp, 1930-1954, 1920-1954 (Box 113)
  - Volume: photo album "by the Shores of Lake Cayuga..." (State Camp at Camp Barton), 1930-1949 (Box 113)
  - Project II- The School Lunch, 1936-1937 (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - Project VI- Cake and Cookies Guide for the 4-H club member, 1937 (Box 143, Folder 16A)
  - New York State Rural Youth Conference- guides, 1949-1950 (Box 114)
  - Report- National Extension Young Adult Planning Conference, 1949; 1953 (Box 114)
  - Older rural youth and young adult programs- minutes, plans of work, reports, 1947-1949 (Box 114)
  - Older rural youth- committee minutes, conferences, etc., 1944-1951 (Box 114)
  - Young Adult Advisory Committee minutes (see also older rural youth), 1949-1953 (Box 114)
  - Annual plan of work and report- older rural youth, 1949 (Box 114)
  - Council of Rural Youth Organizations Advisors meeting, 1954 (Box 114)
  - Manuals- leadership training- New York State Rural Youth Conference (Box 114)
  - Young adult program (Box 114)
  - New York State Rural Youth Conference (Box 114)
  - Young adult program- coordinator job description (Box 114)
  - Young adult program- history (New York State) (Box 114)
  - Young adult program- history (U.S.) (Box 114)
  - Sub-committee on health, 1945 (Box 115)
  - Extension committee- health and safety, 1946 (Box 115)
  - National health program, 1946 (Box 115)
  - College sub-committee- health, nutrition, and safety, 1946 (Box 115)
  - Home and farm safety program, 1947 (Box 115)
  - Health and safety - national contest entries, 1948 (Box 115)
  - Health and safety- national contest entries, 1949 (Box 115)
  - New York State Extension Coordinating Committee- health and safety, 1951-1954 (Box 115)
  - New York State 4-H Club Advisory Health Committee, 1952 (Box 115)
  - Health improvement project and programs (Box 115)
  - Leader's guide for health chairman (Box 115)
  - Health reports (Box 115)
  - Health- 5 minutes of Health (Box 115)
  - Health - curricular letters (Box 115)
  - Health- New York State committee, 1938-1949 (Box 115)
  - Health and safety- material (Box 115)
  - Health (Box 115)
  - #6 Health and Safety (Box 115)
  - #5 Health and Safety (Box 115)
  - #4 Health and Safety (Box 115)
  - Annual conferences - 414, 1919-1924 (Box 115)
  - Annual conferences, 1925-1928 (Box 115)
  - Annual conferences, 1929-1931 (Box 115)
  - Annual conferences, 1932-1935 (Box 115)
  - Annual conferences, 1936-1937 (Box 115)
  - Annual conferences, 1938-1945 (Box 115)
  - Annual conferences, 1948-1949 (Box 115)
  - Minutes and programs of the New York State 4-H Extension Federation annual meetings, 1939; 1940 (Box 116)
  - Central district federation minutes, 1935-1946 (Box 116)
  - Minutes of board directors, constitution and executive committee duties, 1939-1940 (Box 116)
  - New York State Extension Federation- Western New York, 1940-1954 (Box 116)
  - New York State Extension Federation- Western New York, 1940-1954 (Box 116)
  - Western District Federation, 1935-1951 (Box 116)
  - Western District Federation, 1952-1956 (Box 116)
  - Eastern New York, 4-H Club Leader's Association, 1935-1950 (Box 116)
  - Eastern New York, 4-H Club Leader's Association, 1951-1958 (Box 116)
  - South Central District 4-H Conference, 1957 (Box 116)
  - Northern Central District 4-H Conference, 1957 (Box 116)
  - Central District Federation, 1935-1957 (Box 116)
  - Central District Federation- secretary - treasurer's Handbook (Box 116)
  - New York State 4-H Extension Federation, 1935-1956 (Box 116)
  - Plans of work, 1946-1956 (Box 116)
  - Junior Field Days (Club Conference), 1923-1929 (Box 117)
  - Junior Field Days, Club Congress, 1930; 1931 (Box 117)
  - Club Congress, 1932-1935 (Box 117)
  - State club conference, 1936-1958 (Box 117)
  - Early history (Box 118)
  - Semi-annual report, 1940-05-31-1946-06-01 (Box 118)
  - Financial statement 4-H club department, 1950 (Box 118)
  - Financial summary 4-H club department, 1949-1952 (Box 118)
  - Laws relating to extension and 4-H work, 1924-1962 (Box 118)
  - 4-H personnel pictures (Box 118)
  - Liberty Hyde Bailey (Box 118)
  - State club extension, 1924 (Box 118)
  - 4-H miscellaneous (Box 118)
  - 4-H extension, 1924 (Box 118)
  - 4-H extension, 1925-1927 (Box 118)
  - 4-H extension history (Box 118)
  - 4-H Liberty Ship "Carl E. Ladd" (Box 118)
  - 4-H Liberty Ship (Box 118)
  - 4-H bulletins, handbooks, 1903-1918 (Box 118)
  - 4-H bulletins, handbooks, 1926-1950 (Box 118)
  - State national and international winner (Box 118)
    i
  - Report- New York State 4-H Extension Federation, 1949-1955 (Box 118)
  - Summaries of meetings of the extension sub-committee on 4-H club work, 1953-1963 (Box 118)
  - 4-H HAPS, 1937-1960 (Box 119)
  - Boy's and Girls' Club charter (Box 120)
  - Leaflet, "Boys and Trees Grow Up Together" (Box 121)
  - Young adult picture file and notebook, including index (Box 121)
  - 4-H leader training worksheets, assignments, 1960-1969 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - 4-H Sportfishing Aquatic Resources Education Program (SAREP), no date (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Proposal for restructuring the Office of the Cornell Extension Representatives; Associations- campus connections study, 2001, 2002 (Box 143, Folder 55)
  - New York State presentations events, 2001-2008 (Box 143, Folder 56)
  - Celebrating a Century of Leadership and Service, 2002 (Box 143, Folder 57)
  - 4-H uniform history, 1926-2009 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - New York State Extension Committee on 4-H Club Work, 1945-1966 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Science in 4-H Study: A Study of the Possibilities of Expanding the Understanding and use of Science Through 4-H Club Work- conducted by the National Club 4-H Foundation, 1963-04 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Learning for the Future- New York State 4-H Foundation program report, 1973-06 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Partners with Youth- New York State 4-H Foundation, 1972-04 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - 4-H foundation youth development horse program- agriculture and New York State horse breeding development fund, 2013 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Effective utilization and evaluation of 4-H curriculum, 1985-02-25-1985-03-01 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Science and Technology the 4-H Way- status report, 1986 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - Citizenship Washington Focus- participant handbook, 1996 (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - Programming in schools, 1990; Applebee, Glenn (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Protecting the well-being of 4-H youth, 1996-10 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - 4-H youth development external review and strategic plan, 1998-2000 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - 4-H youth development review document, 1999-02 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Report of the external review team of New York State 4-H youth development, 1999-03-24 (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Foundations for Building Remarkable 4-H Youth Development Programs- inservice, 1999 (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Understanding the Difference 4-H Clubs Make in the Lives of New York Youth, 1999 (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - Adopt a Highway Program, 2000-2008 (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Start Something- Tiger Woods Foundation leader guide, 2002 (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - Marketing action team resource guide- for the 4-H youth voices and action public service advertising campaign, no date (Box 146, Folder 11)
  - Citizen U coloring and activity book: Taste the Rainbow, no date (Box 146, Folder 12)
  - 4-H planning- includes strategic plans, 2000-2012 (Box 146, Folder 13)
  - 4-H Career Explorations conference information, 2005-2012 (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - 4-H Career Explorations conference handbooks, 1994, 1996, 2000-2003, 2005-2007, 2016 (Box 148, Folder 12)
  - Conferences, 2008-2015 (Box 146, Folder 14)
  - 4-H science toolkits, 2009 (Box 148, Folder 13)
  - National 4-H conference, 2009-2011 (Box 146, Folder 15)
  - Capital Days, 2010-2012 (Box 146, Folder 16)
  - 4-H science, engineering and technology program "Scientifically Speaking", 2010 (Box 148, Folder 14)
  - FIRST- 4-H robotics programs start up plan, 2010-09-01 (Box 148, Folder 15)
  - Evaluating the 4-H Science Initiative- 4-H national headquarters, 2010-2013 (Box 148, Folder 16)
  - 4-H summer reading programs, 2012 (Box 148, Folder 17)
  - Capital Days- conferences, 2012-2015 (Box 146, Folder 17)
  - Collegiate 4-H community service organization scrapbook, 1991-1995 (Box 149)
  - Collegiate 4-H membership, correspondence, records, 1997-2008 (Box 148, Folder 18)
  - Collegiate 4-H Club handbook, 1998-2003 (Box 148, Folder 19-20)
  - Collegiate 4-H, 2012-2014 (Box 146, Folder 19)
  - Youth development research update, 2013 (Box 146, Folder 20)
  - New York State fair and career explorations, 2014 (Box 146, Folder 21)
  - 4-H National Youth Science Day, 2016 (Box 146, Folder 22)
  - New York State 4-H Capital Days 82nd annual program, 2017-05-21-2017-05-23 (Box 148, Folder 21)
  - Civil rights compliance review report for 4-H programs, 2018 (Box 148, Folder 22)
  - Community as Curriculum- youth community informatics- University of Illinois/Champaign, 2019 (Box 146, Folder 18)
- Series III. 4-H Club Records
  - A. 16 mm Films
    - Partners with Youth, 1972; F-870 (Box 122)
    - Partners with Youth- short version- copy 1, F-871 (Box 122)
    - Youth Can Teach, F-872 (Box 122)
    - 4-H: What's It All About?, F-873 (Box 122)
    - Learning for the Future: 4-H in New York City (Use DVD-1001 in the same box.), F-874 (Box 122)
      Click here to see a digitized version of the film.
      Color film with sound discussing the different programs 4-H sponsors for children in New York City.
      Many of these programs involve children living in the city's housing projects and include horse back riding, sewing, wood shop, and photography classes.
    - Learning for the Future: 4-H in New York City - copy of F-874, DVD-1001 (Box 122)
    - 4-H Spots: Demonstration Reel, F-875 (Box 122)
    - New York Spots: 4-H Leaders, F-876 (Box 122)
    - View of You: No. 1, F-877 (Box 122)
    - 4-H TV Spots, 1974-1975; F-878 (Box 122)
  - B. Videotapes and Discs
    - 4-H Camp (2 tapes), V-5979-V-5980 (Box 144)
    - 4-H Spots, V-5981 (Box 144)
    - 4-H strategic plan, 2000-02-15; V-5982 (Box 144)
    - 4-H centennial coverage- CBS's The Saturday Early Show, 2002-08-17; V-5983 (Box 144)
    - 4-H Hidden Valley Camp, V-5984 (Box 144)
    - 4-H Camp Sacandaga, 1988; V-5985 (Box 144)
    - 4-H Camp Arnot and county projects, 1987; V-5986 (Box 144)
    - "Clothes for Independent Living"- U-matic videocassette, 1982-07; V-5987 (Box 144)
    - Cutaways- U-matic videocassettes, 1985-09; V-5988-V-5989 (Box 144)
      Atkin, Gret
    - Camp brochure, 2001; ZD-5 (Box 144)
    - 4-H banner and display, 2004; CD-3877
    - 4-H in Action PowerPoint, 2004; CD-3888
    - Youth Community Action, Niagara County's Outdoor Club PowerPoint, 2005; CD-3893
    - New York State Shooting Sport PowerPoint, 2006-04; CD-3899
    - 4-H Teen Press Corps, 2005-08-28; CD-3854
      Includes 4-H Forum
    - 4-H Teen Press Corps, 2007-08-26; CD-3854
      Clover Connection and photos
    - C.I.T.Y. Project, 2007; CD-3907
    - Forms, memos, New York State 4-H Club Leader Handbook and New York State 4-H Club Management Notebook for Staff, 2007-2010; CD-3901
      Includes photos and Clover Connection
    - Northeast recognition packets, 2008; CD-3904
    - John Losey interview, Date Unknown; CD-3855
    - Steve Hamilton interview, Date Unknown; CD-3856-3857
    - Steve Smith and Susan Hoskins interview about the Institute for Resource Information Sciences (IRIS), 2009-11-06; CD-3861
  - C. Records
    - New York State 4-H club history, 1919-1965 (Box 125, Folder 25)
    - New York State 4-H club history, 1919-1986 (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - New York State 4-H club history, 1940-1949 (Box 125, Folder 24)
    - New York State 4-H clubs, 1942 (Box 143)
    - New York State 4-H clubs, 1960-1979 (Box 143, Folder 19)
    - 4-H policies, 1952-1986 (Box 141, Folder 16)
    - Speeches, 1960-1969 (Box 143, Folder 20)
    - Response to the 4-H task force, 1969; Smith, E.H. (Box 143, Folder 45)
    - Hazardous occupations order- memos, guidelines, 1960-1969 (Box 143, Folder 21)
    - The Evolution of 4-H Work in the United States, 1964-02; Simons, L.F. (Box 143, Folder 22)
    - New York 4-H Agents and Their Association, 1966-01 (Box 143, Folder 23)
    - Round the Year with 4-H Clubs (Box 143, Folder 24)
    - Program development flyers, 1967-1972 (Box 143, Folder 25)
    - Volunteerism- Mildred Fizer, 1971 (Box 143, Folder 26)
    - Tractor safety and certification, 1980-1989 (Box 143, Folder 32)
    - Flowing grain entrapment- grain safety and farmstead safety, 1993 (Box 143, Folder 46)
    - Public relations, 1970-1989 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - 4-H activities, 1970-1999 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Youth building, 1970-1999 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - State fair train rides, 1970-1999 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - State fair handbooks, 1970-1999 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Dress revue, 1960-1999 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - State Fair- miscellaneous, 1970-1999 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - History (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Teen leader programs, 1970-1999 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Judges, 1970-1994 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Budget, 1970-1999 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Fair assistants (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - State Fair Advisory Committee, 1960-1989 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - State Fair evaluations, 1970-1999 (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Evaluation/Stats, 1980-1999 (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Youth building long range program (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - Premium list- various ones, 1921-1996 (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - State fair photos/slides/negatives (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - State 4-H Advisory Committee, 1970-1979 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - State 4-H Advisory Committee, 1979-1985 (Box 125, Folder 2)